{
    "id": "c32008805af843f9ac81fd15be2043aa",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "English ………………… all over the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speaks",
                "is spoken",
                "has spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e19a3f482cdf4d1d899cef16a23408b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The program …………………. by millions of people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "was watched",
                "has watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "178d002a514a4e729fadf4306a5aae38"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief ....................... by the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has arrested",
                "has been arrested",
                "had arrested"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "38eeb8a193f8469a857d8b624f13ea10"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wuthering Heights ………………….. by Emile Bronte.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has written",
                "has been writing",
                "was written"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f321197eb4b14dc2a5dc5ed1d0cfbe49"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys ………………… the wounded man.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "helped",
                "were helped",
                "had helped"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5b72f61239184aa68dcdd19ccf93ff82"
        },
        {
            "question": "Football ..................... all over the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "plays",
                "is played",
                "has played"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4acd5bb506ef4362babc2cd4cd8c6652"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team ....................... the match.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will win",
                "will be won",
                "has been won"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ecb96f2c732049b193da69ceed6e1385"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "confirmed",
                "has confirmed",
                "has been confirmed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6069e2a2200b453888e876473d96561b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The house …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is painting",
                "is being painted",
                "has painted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "14d8891c1a714388882ca77104c350fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "A bridge ....................... by the government.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "built",
                "has built",
                "is being built"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d186aff0e1a9416080eb2d48f10c7d83"
        }
    ]
}